Smith
The College of Saint Rose Archives
- General Correspondence, 1947-1995
  - Letter to Ursula from Sister Margaret Frances Kelly, regarding a commemorative convocation and inauguration of President Miele, 02/22/1971 (Box 1)
  - Letter from President Miele regarding physical facilities changes at the college, August 1971 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Ursula from President Miele regarding contributions to the annual fund drives, 11/10/1971 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Thomas A. Manion to Ursula Smith re: recipient of the Sister Rita Agnes Casey scholarship in Music, 05/02/1977 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Ursula from Mary Murabito, Director of Alumni and Parent Relations about the Founder's Day Liturgy, 04/05/1995 (Box 1)
- Saint Rose Alumni Association, 1934-1990
  - Booklet, "Tenth Anniversary of the Class of '24." The cover says "Urt Casey Smith.", 06/10/1934 (Box 1)
  - Program, "Silver Jubilee Dinner Commemorating the Twenty-fifth Anniversary of the Founding of The College of Saint Rose." Includes signatures of attendees., 11/17/1945 (Box 1)
  - Alumnae Association Full Tuition Scholarship, 1948-1952, in honor of Sister Rita Agnes (Box 1)
  - College of Saint Rose Alumnae Association Annual Dues notice: addressed to Mrs. Smith with her 1959 dues, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - "The Power of .04%": booklet from the Office of the President regarding financial support. Handwritten note written in pencil on the back cover., 10/06/1958 (Box 1)
  - "Rosetta." Vol. XXIII. No. 3.: birth announcement on page 5 for the granddaughter of Casey Smith, and daughter of Ursula Smith McKegney, October 1958 (Box 1)
  - “St. Rose Alumni News," Vol. 1, No. 2: photograph on page 2 of Casey Smith and classmates at the inauguration of President Miele., Spring 1971 (Box 1)
  - "The Newsletter," Vol. 3, No. 3: Casey Smith is listed as a donor on page 4 and 5. Ursula Smith McKegney on page 6., October 1972 (Box 1)
  - College of Saint Rose Alumni Directory and Constitution and By-Laws: notes on pages 54 and 69., 1972 (Box 1)
  - "CSR Update." Vol. I, No. 1: Ursula Smith listed as Phonothon participant on page 7., Spring 1977 (Box 1)
  - "CSR Update." IV, No. 2. Donor Recognition Issue: Casey Smith mentioned on pages 11, 15, and 25. Ursula Smith McKegney mentioned on page 18, Winter 1981 (Box 1)
  - Golden Roses Society Lifetime Membership card for Ursula Casey Smith, awarded in recognition of 50 years as an alumna Letter, 06/08/1990 (Box 1)
- Archconfraternity of St. Joseph Norbertine Order, 1979
  - Informational Pamphlet "The Archconfraternity of St. Joseph and the Norbertine Order", 1979 (Box 1)
  - Brochure - St. Norbert Abbey, 1979 (Box 1)
- Diplomas and Awards, 1946 and 1985-1986
  - Delta Epsilon Sigma, Honor of Membership Certificate, Awarded to Sister Rita Agnes, 05/21/1946 (Box 1)
  - College of Saint Rose Founders' Club: Awarded to Ursula R. Smith, 1985 (Box 1)
  - College of Saint Rose Founders' Club: Awarded to Ursula R. Smith, 1986 (Box 1)
- Saint Rose Memorabilia, 1926-1995
  - Two drinking glasses, "75 1920-1995. The College of Saint Rose, 75 Years of Distinction" in blue print. (Box 2)
  - Two drinking glasses, "College of Saint Rose" with college seal, all in yellow print., undated (Box 2)
  - Dance card, "College of Saint Rose Alumnae Informal Dance 1926 Auditorium October twenty-second." Five-sided black booklet on a yellow tassel. The card has five names listed and likely belonged to Ursula Casey Smith., 10/26/1926 (Box 2)
  - Dance card, "CSR Sophomore Soiree '51." The booklet is rectangular and attached to a blue tassel. There are seven names listed., 05/13/1949 (Box 2)
  - Dance booklet, "Junior Promenade, Class of 1927." The square booklet has a red leather cover and pages for each girl in the class to leave notes. Some pages are filled out., 02/12/1926 (Box 2)
  - Dance booklet, "College of Saint Rose Class of 1951 Senior Ball." Booklet is rectangular with a shiny green cover with the college seal, and is attached to a silver string and foam backing. Anne Smith is listed as a committee member and Mr. and Mrs. Edward J. Smith as patrons., 12/01/1950 (Box 2)
  - Dance booklet, "Junior Prom - 1948 College of St. Rose." Small rectangular booklet with plastic faux pearl cover with gold writing. Attached to a white tassel., 02/06/1948 (Box 2)
  - Dance booklet, "Junior Promenade Class of 1928." The booklet is badge-shaped and has a blue-swirled hard cover with a white tassel., 02/11/1927 (Box 2)
  - Tickets (2), pink, "Reserved Seat: Rose Day College of Saint Rose.", undated (Box 2)
  - Name card, rectangular. "Ursula Casey Smith, Silver Jubilee of the Class of '24." White with black writing and silver flowers and trim., 1949 (Box 2)
  - Playing card container, blue-gray leather container labeled "Bridge" with the college seal in gold writing. The container holds two decks of cards, one blue with a Roman figure and one pink with black and silver designs., undated (Box 2)
  - Collection of book plates, "Ex Libris Ursula R. Casey," wrapped with a blue band labeled "Sr. Rose.", undated (Box 2)
  - "CSR Hooked on Swing" wine glasses (2). Glass with red writing, [ca. mid 1980s], 1980-1989 (Box 3)
  - "College of Saint Rose Inaugural Ball." Plastic mug., 11/19/1983 (Box 3)
  - Dance Favor(Reddish vinyl box with St. Rose crest, lined with velvet.), 1950-1959 (Box 3)
  - Plastic Keepsake from Inaugural Celebration (dried flowers in plastic pod)., 10/05/1996 (Box 3)
  - Glass Dish, "Picotte Hall, The College of Saint Rose, September 21, 1977, Dedicated Albany, New York." Gold and white on textured glass., 09/21/1977 (Box 3)
  - Button, "Congrads Dr. Mom", undated (Box 3)
  - Button (photograph) Dr. Manion., undated (Box 3)
  - Button (name tag), "Sr. Rose. Celebrate CSR", undated (Box 3)
  - Graduation Tassel, burgundy and cream, Class of 1951 (belonging to Anne nee Smith, daughter of Ursula Casey Smith. (Box 3)
  - Graduation Tassel, black (possibly Ursula's), undated (Box 3)
  - Graduation Tassel, gold and white (probably belonging to Urt's daughters Sr. Rose or Ursula), undated (Box 3)
  - Graduation Tassel, gold and white (probably belonging to Urt's daughters Sr. Rose or Ursula), undated (Box 3)
  - Pins (2), "Golden Roses, College of St. Rose, 50 Yrs.", 1970 (Box 3)
  - Pin, "CSR." Cream colored with gold writing and trim., undated (Box 3)
  - Pin, wooden letters spell "St. Rose" with yellow and white ribbons attached to the bottom., undated (Box 3)
  - Pin, "May Day 1957." White with blue writing and white and blue ribbons attached to the bottom. (Box 3)
  - Charm, College of Saint Rose crest. Black with gold edges, possibly a worn on a necklace., undated (Box 3)
  - Plastic tube from the 75th Anniversary celebration of Saint Rose, with rolled document inside: "Please accept this seedling as an expression of our appreciation for your continuing commitment to The College of Saint Rose." Also includes instructions for planting the Blue Spruce seeding., 1995 (Box 3)
  - Button (name tag), "Sr. Rose. Saint Rose Night, September 17, 1993." NOTE: Item not found during last inventory (3/3/2004), 09/17/1993 (Box 3)